<?xml version="1.0"?>
<digitalAssetContract version="2.0">

<entity shortname="Satoshi"
longname="Satoshi Nakamoto" 
email="satoshi@nakamoto.com"/>

<issue company="Swedish Coins"
email="info@swedishcoins.net"
contractUrl="https://swedishcoins.net/contract"
type="currency"/>

<currency name="Bitcoins" tla="BTC" symbol="BTC" type="decimal" factor="1000" decimal_power="3" fraction="mBTC"/>

<!-- CONDITIONS -->

<condition name="backing">
  Digital Bitcoins are payable to bearer in blockchain Bitcoins,
  at any exchange provider supporting our contract in any denomination
  they support, or through one of our direct agents in 100 BTC increments.
</condition>

<condition name="audit">
  Bitcoins are audited monthly by highly trusted people.
</condition>

<condition name="purchase">
  In order to obtain Bitcoins, you must purchase them from an exchange
  provider or receive them in trade.
  The issuer only accepts direct bail-in of blockchain Bitcoins from an
  authorized exchange provider.
</condition>

<condition name="redemption">
  In order to redeem Digital Bitcoins, you must use an exchange provider.
  If none are available you must make sure you trust this issuer
  and make sure this contract is enforceable in your jurisdiction,
  and make sure you are trading in a BASKET currency so that you
  are not entirely reliant on a single issuer.
  Digital Bitcoins are redeemable to exchange providers in 100 BTC increments.
</condition>

<condition name="rate">
  Issuance and redemption will be performed at no charge.
</condition>

<condition name="buyback">
  The Issuer reserves the right to buy back all outstanding
  currency, thereby terminating the use of this instrument.
</condition>

<condition name="liability">
  Bitcoins and their blockchain are solely liable to perform according to
  the conditions specified in this contract.
</condition>

<condition name="mint">
  Float - the total quantity of Bitcoins is created by Satoshi Nakamoto.
  The quantity of Bitcoins that enter the market yearly is strictly
  regulated by cryptographic algorithms.

  Any server operator using this contract will not issue any more
  digital BTC currency than he actually has in blockchain Bitcoins.
</condition>

<condition name="privacy">
  The purchase, redemption and trading of digital assets normally
  are done on the basis of strong privacy.
</condition>

</digitalAssetContract>
