<?xml version="1.0"?>
<notaryProviderContract version="2.0">

<entity shortname="Transactions.com" 
longname="Transactions.com, LLC" 
email="serverfarm@cloudcomputing.com"
serverURL="https://transactions.com/vers/1/"/>

<notaryServer hostname="localhost" 
 port="7085"
 URL="https://transactions.com/vers/1/" />

<condition name="backing">
  Transactions.com does not issue any currencies or digital assets,
  and does not back any of the same. You are solely responsible for
  whom you choose to trade with. 
</condition>

<condition name="audit">
Transactions.com operates open-source OpenTransactions software, and
code audits are randomly performed by CodeNotary.com
Our insurance company is:  GeicoCurrency.com
</condition>

<condition name="rate">
  Transaction credits may be purchased on our website, the fees for which
  are posted there also. We make money solely from transaction processing,
  that is, providing an electronic notary service for others, for a usage fee.
</condition>

<condition name="liability">
  Issuers are solely liable to perform according to
  the conditions specified in their asset contracts.
  Transactions.com is liable to keep transactions secure and clean.
</condition>

<condition name="mint">
  Float - the total quantity of any digital asset outstanding -
  is created by the issuer from his own mint, and signed by his private key.
  
  Disbursements from the Mint account are to be made on receipt of
  duly signed and public authorization from the Issuer.  All
  disbursements from the Mint account are to be made to the single
  Currency Comptroller account identified by the authorization.

  From time to time, the Currency Comptroller may direct the
  Currency Manager to return digital assets to the Mint
  for the express purpose of reducing the float. Digital assets
  so delivered are to be deposited into the Mint account,
  thus reducing the float by that amount.
</condition>

<condition name="privacy">
  The purchase, redemption and trading at Transactions.com normally
  are done on the basis of strong privacy. We will never release any of
  your information unless compelled by law.
</condition>

</notaryProviderContract>
