<?xml version="1.0"?>
<digitalAssetContract version="2.0">

<entity shortname="Gnome" 
longname="The Gnomes of Zurich" 
email="gnome@zurich.com"/>

<issue company="Anon-E-Gold, Inc" 
email="gnome@anonesilver.com"
contractUrl="https://e-silver.com/cash/contract/"
type="currency"/>

<currency name="silver grams" tla="GRAM" symbol="sg" type="decimal" factor="1" decimal_power="0" fraction="mg"/>

<!-- CONDITIONS -->

<condition name="backing">
  DIGITAL SILVER GRAMS are payable to bearer in physical silver grams,
  at any exchange provider supporting our contract in any denomination
  they support, or through one of our direct agents in 1000 oz bars. 
</condition>

<condition name="audit">
  Silver Grams are audited monthly by highly trusted people.
</condition>

<condition name="purchase">
  In order to obtain Silver Grams, you must
  purchase them from an exchange provider or receive them in trade.
  The issuer only accepts direct bail-in of physical silver from an
  authorized exchange provider.
</condition>

<condition name="redemption">
  In order to redeem Silver Grams, you must use an exchange provider.
  If none are available you must make sure you trust this issuer
  and make sure this contract is enforceable in your jurisdiction,
  and make sure you are trading in a BASKET currency so that you
  are not entirely reliant on a single issuer.
  Silver Grams are redeemable to exchange providers in 1 oz coins.
</condition>

<condition name="rate">
  Issuance and redemption will be performed at no charge.
</condition>

<condition name="buyback">
  The Issuer reserves the right to buy back all outstanding
  currency, thereby terminating the use of this instrument.
</condition>

<condition name="liability">
  Silver and its maker, God, are solely liable to perform according to
  the conditions specified in this contract.
</condition>

<condition name="mint">
  Float - the total quantity of Silver is created by God.
  The quantity of silver that enters the market yearly is strictly
  regulated by His wisdom. 

  Any server operator using this contract will not issue any more
  silver digital currency than he actually has in physical silver.
</condition>

<condition name="privacy">
  The purchase, redemption and trading of digital assets normally
  are done on the basis of strong privacy.
</condition>

</digitalAssetContract>
