<?xml version="1.0"?>
<digitalAssetContract version="2.0">

<entity shortname="Just testing" 
longname="I need user feedback to help design the contract tags the server must support..." 
email="F3llowTraveler (at)  gmail.com"/>

<issue company="Chuck-E-Cheese, Inc" 
email="games@chuckecheese.com"
contractUrl="https://chuckecheese.com/games/contract/"
type="currency"/>

<currency name="game tokens" tla="TOKEN" symbol="tks" type="decimal" factor="1" decimal_power="0" fraction="mg"/>

<!-- CONDITIONS -->

<condition name="backing">
  Chuck-E-Cheese's Game Tokens are payable to bearer in fun video game
  entertainment, on demand, subject to the conditions specified in this
  currency contract.

  Chuck will maintain at all times a primary reserve of old 1980s
  video games in an amount sufficient to satisfy all the tokens in circulation.
</condition>

<condition name="audit">
  Chuck-E-Cheese's Game Tokens are primarily backed by Chucky's
  reputation as a connossieur of fine pizza.

  No primary reserve is established for this currency.
</condition>

<condition name="purchase">
  In order to obtain Chuck-E-Cheese's Game Tokens, you must
  persuade Chuck to part with same, by any means fair
  or foul. Common means are in exchange for favours
  done to Chuck or in exchange for national currency.
</condition>

<condition name="redemption">
  In order to redeem Chuck-E-Cheese's Game Tokens, you must
  negotiate a suitable time and place, and then ask
  nicely. Because most suitable redemption locations
  (game section of pizza parlor) do not have Internet access,
  it is likely that there will be a time delay between
  currency redemption and arrival of available games.
</condition>

<condition name="rate">
  Issuance and redemption will be performed at no charge.
</condition>

<condition name="buyback">
  The Issuer reserves the right to buy back all outstanding
  currency, thereby terminating the use of this instrument.
</condition>

<condition name="liability">
  Chuck the rat is solely liable to perform according to
  the conditions specified in this contract.
</condition>

<condition name="mint">
  Float - the total quantity of Chuck-E-Cheese's Game Tokens
  outstanding - is created by a Mint account,
  specially set by the Operator.  Authorization to the Operator
  is hereby included to specially set one Mint account for creation
  of Chuck-E-Cheese's Game Tokens.

  Disbursements from the Mint account are to be made on receipt of
  duly signed and public authorization from Chuck the Rat.  All
  disbursements from the Mint account are to be made to the single
  Currency Comptroller account identified by the authorization.

  From time to time, the Currency Comptroller may direct the
  Currency Manager to return Chuck-E-Cheese's Game Tokens to the Mint
  for the express purpose of reducing the float. Chuck-E-Cheese's Game Tokens
  so delivered are to be deposited into the Mint account,
  thus reducing the float by that amount.
</condition>

<condition name="privacy">
  The purchase, redemption and trading of Chuck-E-Cheese's Game Tokens normally
  are done on the basis of strong privacy.
</condition>

</digitalAssetContract>
